cyberindian.com 2013-03-21

# Privacy Policy for Cyberindian.com website

**Privacy Policy**

The privacy of our visitors to Cyberindian.com is very important to us and we are 100% committed to privacy. 

At Cyberindian.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you visit Cyberindian.com, and how we safeguard the information we thus collected. 

Cyberindian.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We do not sell, share, rent, forward or give away your personal information to anyone in any manner.

**Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or MTNL, VSNL etc), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

Your IP address is automatically logged by our Apache webserver. However that information is only used statistically to find out the reach of this website. All the logs are automatically discarded every couple of months. Non-identifying aggregate information may be retained.

**Information Collected**

We use tools including third-party tools to collect selective user information from our users during their period of stay and use of information, graphics, images and content at Cyberindian.com.

We gather selective generic information with respect to customers’ use of our web site, such as the number of unique visitors, the frequency with which they visit, selective demographic details and the areas on the web site that they prefer. We only look at the data on a collective basis, in summary form, rather than on an individual basis. This statistical data does not contain any personally identifiable information about you or any of our users.

**Your email address**

Your email address in all submitted articles and website based forms like contact-us form etc is never sold to anyone for any reason or consideration. It is only used to provide you your subscribed services at our site and occasionally communicate with you to inform you important updates to this site.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

A cookie is a piece of information which is designed to be stored on your computer’s hard drive by your web browser. 

_**We DO NOT USE COOKIES! on Cyberindian.com website and we don’t need them!**_

We also use third party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. Some of these advertising companies may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they serve ads on our website, which will also send these advertising companies (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New Delhi real estate ads to someone from New Delhi) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. 

Questions regarding this privacy statement, should be sent via e-mail :  [contact@cyberindian.com](mailto:contact@cyberindian.com)

**Cyberindian.com**  
12, Chandresh Tower, Jesal Park,  
Bhayandar (East) - 401 105  
Maharashtra, India
